syncing.net 2007-02-18

# Sync Outlook without a server on multiple computers and notebooks

### TERMS OF USE

### DISCLAIMER

1\. Content

The author reserves the right not to be responsible for the topicality, correctness, completeness or quality of the information provided. Liability claims regarding damage caused by the use of any information provided, including any kind of information which is incomplete or incorrect, will therefore be rejected. All offers are non-binding and without obligation. Parts of the pages or the complete publication including all offers and information might be extended, changed or partly or completely deleted by the author without separate announcement. 

2\. Referrals and links

The author is not responsible for any content linked or referred to from his pages - unless he has full knowledge of illegal contents and would be able to prevent the visitors of his site from viewing those pages. If any damage occurs by the use of information presented there, only the author of the respective pages might be liable, not the one who has linked to these pages. Furthermore the author is not liable for any postings or messages published by users of discussion boards or mailinglists provided on his page. 

3\. Copyright

The author intended not to use any copyrighted material for the publication or, if not possible, to indicate the copyright of the respective object. The copyright for any material created by the author is reserved. Any duplication or use of objects such as diagrams, sounds or texts in other electronic or printed publications is not permitted without the author's agreement. 

4\. Privacy policy

If the opportunity for the input of personal or business data (email addresses, name, addresses) is given, the input of this data takes place voluntarily. The use and payment of all offered services are permitted - if and so far technically possible and reasonable - without specification of any personal data or under specification of anonymizated data or an alias. 

5\. Legal validity of this disclaimer

This disclaimer is to be regarded as part of the internet publication from which you were referred. If sections or individual terms of this statement are not legal or correct, the content or validity of the other parts remain uninfluenced by this fact. 

LIMITATION OF LIABILITY

SYNCING.NET SHALL NOT BE LIABLE FOR ANY DAMAGES SUFFERED AS A RESULT OF USING, MODIFYING, CONTRIBUTING, COPYING, DISTRIBUTING, OR DOWNLOADING THE MATERIALS. IN NO EVENT SHALL SYNCING.NET BE LIABLE FOR ANY INDIRECT, PUNITIVE, SPECIAL, INCIDENTAL, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGE (INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO LOSS OF BUSINESS, REVENUE, PROFITS, USE, DATA OR OTHER ECONOMIC ADVANTAGE), HOWEVER IT ARISES, WHETHER IN AN ACTION OF CONTRACT, NEGLIGENCE OR OTHER TORTIOUS ACTION, ARISING OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE USE OR PERFORMANCE OF INFORMATION AVAILABLE FROM THIS WEB SITE, EVEN IF SYNCING.NET HAS BEEN PREVIOUSLY ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGE. YOU HAVE SOLE RESPONSIBILITY FOR THE ADEQUATE PROTECTION AND BACKUP OF DATA AND/OR EQUIPMENT USED IN CONNECTION WITH THE WEB SITE AND YOU WILL NOT MAKE A CLAIM AGAINST SYNCING.NET FOR LOST DATA, RE-RUN TIME, INACCURATE OUTPUT, WORK DELAYS, OR LOST PROFITS RESULTING FROM THE USE OF THE MATERIALS. YOU AGREE TO HOLD SYNCING.NET HARMLESS FROM, AND YOU COVENANT NOT TO SUE SYNCING.NET FOR, ANY CLAIMS BASED ON OR RELATED TO THE USE OF THE WEB SITE. 

* * *

### PRIVACY POLICY

Thank you for visiting the SYNCING.NET website located at www.syncing.net. SYNCING.NET is concerned about personal privacy and is committed to protecting the privacy of visitors to our website. This Privacy Policy identifies the personally identifiable information that SYNCING.NET collects about you at our website and describes how SYNCING.NET uses and protects such information. 

IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH ANY OF THE TERMS BELOW, YOU SHOULD NOT USE THIS WEBSITE OR THE SERVICES OFFERED BY SYNCING.NET ON THE WEBSITE. BY USING THIS WEBSITE, YOU ARE AGREEING TO THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY. 

What Information Is Collected

You may visit our website and learn about SYNCING.NET on the website anonymously. The data that we regularly collect about visitors to our website (e.g. browser type, pages accessed, duration of visit, etc.) does not enable us to identify you. 

We collect personally identifiable information about you only if you voluntarily provide it to us when you buy a SYNCING.NET product. You are required to provide your email address, address, country of residence, state and postal code. We may also ask you, but you are not required to provide, information regarding how you learned about SYNCING.NET. 

Use of Information

We use your contact information to proceed with the purchase and billing process and to contact you when reasonably necessary. We may also use any information you have provided as reasonably necessary to administer or provide customer support for the website and for the SYNCING.NET products. We use the information submitted by you to send you correspondence and other information that may interest you and to respond to your correspondence. If, for any reason, you would like to be removed from our email list, you can send us an email at [info@syncing.net](mailto:info@syncing.net). 

Disclosure of Information

We do not sell, rent or lease your personally identifiable information to third parties. However, we may disclose your personally identifiable information in certain limited circumstances: 

a. | We may send email offers to selected groups of SYNCING.NET users on behalf of our company and on behalf of other businesses in whose products and services you may have an interest; but we will not disclose any of your personally identifiable information to any such businesses. We will also include in each such email instructions as to how you can permanently opt out of receiving any such future emails.   
---|---  
b. | We also reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information if we reasonably believe we are required to do so by law, regulation or other government authority.   
c. | Finally, we may disclose your personally identifiable information upon a transfer or sale to another entity of all or substantially all of SYNCING.NET's assets or stock in SYNCING.NET's line of business to which this privacy policy relates or upon any other corporate reorganization. (If, for example, in the future, we undergo any sort of corporate reorganization, we may need to transfer your personally identifiable information to the surviving entity.)  

Cookies 

Cookies are files that your web browser places on your computer's hard drive. They tell us whether you have visited our website previously. We issue a session cookie only to record encrypted authentication information for the duration of a specific session. The session cookie includes neither the username or nor the password of the user. 

Security Measures 

Our website employs procedural and technological measures consistent with legal requirements and the demands of customer service, that are reasonably designed to protect your personally identifiable information from loss, misuse or unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction, including using secure servers for data storage. 

Policy Changes 

Due to the Internet's rapidly evolving nature, SYNCING.NET may need to update this Privacy Policy from time to time. If so, SYNCING.NET will post its updated policy on this system. We encourage you to review this Privacy Policy regularly for any changes. 

Questions

If you have any questions related to this Privacy Policy please send us an email at [info@syncing.net](mailto:info@syncing.net). 

* * *

END-USER LICENSE AGREEMENT FOR SYNCING.NET for Outlook®

This End-User License Agreement (EULA) is a legal agreement between you (either an individual or a single entity) and SYNCING.NET Technologies GmbH Berlin (SYNCING.NET) for the software product identified above, which includes computer software and may include associated media, printed materials, and online or electronic documentation (SOFTWARE PRODUCT). By installing, copying, or otherwise using the SOFTWARE PRODUCT, you agree to be bound by the terms of this EULA. If you do not agree to the terms of this EULA, do not install or use the SOFTWARE PRODUCT. Please do NOT order a license key if you do not agree to this EULA. 

License Conditions

The SOFTWARE PRODUCT is protected by copyright laws and international copyright treaties, as well as other intellectual property laws and treaties. This also applies to demo versions. No part of the software or the manual may be multiplied, disseminated or processed in any way without the written consent of SYNCING.NET. Violations of these conditions will be prosecuted in every case. The use of the software is done at your own risk. The manufacturer and developer accept no liability for any damages, either as a direct or indirect consequence of the use of this product or software. The SOFTWARE PRODUCT is licensed, not sold. 

Grant of License

This EULA grants you the following rights: 

Distribution

You may install and use one copy of the SOFTWARE PRODUCT, or any prior version for the same operating system, on a single computer. The primary user of the computer on which the SOFTWARE PRODUCT is installed may make a second copy for his or her exclusive use. 

Storage/Network Use

You may also store or install a copy of the SOFTWARE PRODUCT on a storage device, such as a network server, used only to install or run the SOFTWARE PRODUCT on your other computers over an internal network; however, you must acquire and dedicate a license for each separate computer on which the SOFTWARE PRODUCT is installed or run from the storage device. A license for the SOFTWARE PRODUCT may not be shared or used concurrently on different computers. 

Restrictions

You may not reverse engineer, decompile, or disassemble the SOFTWARE PRODUCT, except and only to the extent that such activity is expressly permitted by applicable law notwithstanding this limitation. 

Termination

Without prejudice to any other rights, SYNCING.NET may terminate this EULA if you fail to comply with the terms and conditions of this EULA. In such event, you must destroy all copies of the SOFTWARE PRODUCT and all of its component parts. 

If you have any questions on this EULA, please send an email to [info@syncing.net](mailto:info@syncing.net) or write to: 

SYNCING.NET Technologies GmbH

Torellstr. 1  
D-10243 Berlin  
GERMANY  

SYNCING.NET for Outlook®  
Copyright © 2006-2007 SYNCING.NET Technologies GmbH. All rights reserved. 

Third-party Trademarks:

  * Outlook is a registered trademark of Microsoft Corporation. 
  * Groove and Groove Virtual Office are registered trademarks of Groove Networks, Inc. 
  * FolderShare is a registered trademark of ByteTaxi, Inc.
